- You ready to order?
- One moment.
(Sheldon:)I'm conducting an experiment.
(Howard:)With Dungeons and Dragons dice?
(Sheldon:)Yes. From here on in...
(Sheldon:)...I've decided to make all trivial
decisions with a throw of the dice.
(Sheldon:)Thus freeing up my mind
to do what it does best...
(Sheldon:)...enlighten and amaze.
(Sheldon:)Page 14, item seven.
(Howard:)So, what's for dinner?
(Sheldon:)A side of corn succotash.
(Sheldon:)Hmm, interesting.
(Penny:)Um, Howard,
can I see you for a minute, please?
Ugh, I don't wanna show any more of your
friends how I can fit in the booster seats.
(Penny:)Uh, no, that's not it.
Just come with me, please?
(Sheldon:)Let's see what I'll be washing
that succotash down with.
(Sheldon:)A pitcher of margaritas.